# Songyu Wang

# Software Engineer in Test at Heartflow, Inc

Software test engineer with experience in medical device industry (regulated). Heavily involved in test design, test automation, test framework development, and test framework maintenance. Collaborated daily with development teams to ensure the quality of the products. Produced various testrelated documentation to meet regulatory compliance. Familiar with Scrum practice.



wangsongyuf@gmail.com



1812-201-9470



Redwood City, CA, United States



songyu-wang.github.io

#### in

linkedin.com/in/wangsongyu



github.com/Songyu-Wang

## SKILLS

Python

Matlab

SauceLabs

**Cypress** 

Selenium

Mailosaur

Behave

HTML + CSS + JavaScript

Ruby on Rails

MySQL and Similar SQL databases

MongoDB

Redis

Neo4i

AWS

Hadoop

Jenkins

Docker

Google Cloud

Scalr

Jira

Confluence

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# Software Engineer in Test

## HeartFlow, Inc 🗷

07/2018 - Present

Redwood City, CA

- Supported three internal and external UI products
- Developed and maintained existing legacy Frontend test frameworks
- Designed and Implemented two new Frontend test frameworks
- Designed manual and automated tests to verify frontend product requirements
- Automated manual tests to improve test automation rate
- Performed verification and validation activities before releasing product updates. E.g. creating test plans, executing functional tests, collaborating system level testing across teams/components, etc.
- Produced and examined various deployment and test related documentation that meets regulatory compliance
- Practiced Scrum agile framework
- Previous Software Engineer in Test, Intern from 05/2017 to 08/2017

#### Software Intern

#### Rose-Hulman Ventures 🗷

02/2017 - 05/2017

Terre Haute, IN

- Implemented and improved a multi-platform(Web/IOS) application
- Designed multiple versions of mobile app UI
- Implemented features for programmable logic controller

### **Prior Work Experience**

Details are omitted to conserve space. See https://songyu-wanq.github.io/

- Software Intern at Pansoft Co. Ltd.(Jinan, China)
- Teaching Assistant at Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology(Terre Haute, IN)

## **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science**

# Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology &

08/2014 - 05/2018

Terre Haute, IN

- GPA: 3.73/4
- Double Major: Computer Science major and Software Engineering major
- Minors: Mathematics minor, Computational Science minor, and Data Science minor
- □ Senior Project: Popular Media, a media content selling website, proposed by Popular Pays, Inc. (Chicago, IL). Used Ember.js, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL and Google Cloud Vision
- Member of Upsilon Pi Epsilon(YΠE): International Honor Society for the Computing and Information Disciplines
- Member of the Order of the Engineer

# **CERTIFICATES**

Professional Scrum Product Owner I (07/2019 – Present)

Issuing Organization: Scrum.org

Professional Scrum Master I (11/2018 - Present)

Issuing Organization: Scrum.org

MTA: Software Development Fundamentals (11/2016 – Present)

Issuing Organization: Microsoft